* Outsource Something
    
    
    
    [
    
    Outsourcing Companies
    
    A collection of top-rated outsourcing companies](https://gigworker.com/outsourcing-companies)[
    
    Freelancer Directory
    
    Find top-rated freelancers to outsource work to](https://gigworker.com/freelancers)
    
    [Recruitment Services
    
    ](https://gigworker.com/services/recruitment)
    
    How it Works

    Submit a Listing

* Find a Gig
    
    
    
    [
    
    Jobs
    
    Browse the best freelance jobs, gigs, and tasks available](https://gigworker.com/jobs)[
    
    Companies
    
    Find gig-related companies that are currently hiring gig workers](https://gigworker.com/companies)[
    
    Side Hustles
    
    Browse an extensive list of side hustles to find one you love](https://gigworker.com/side-hustles)
    
    [Gig & Product Reviews
    
    ](https://gigworker.com/reviews)
    
    Collections

    Our Favorites

* Level Up
    
    
    
    [
    
    Gig Headquarters
    
    Information about working with specific gig platforms](https://gigworker.com/gig-headquarters)[
    
    Upskilling Guides
    
    How to do popular side hustles and gigs](https://gigworker.com/upskilling)[
    
    Enhancements
    
    Products, services & training to help you earn more](https://gigworker.com/enhancements)[
    
    Community
    
    Social groups, forums, training courses, and digital downloadables](https://community.gigworker.com/)
    
    [Basics of Gig Work
    
    ](https://www.gigworker.com/blog-category/gig-economy)
    
    Other

    Fundamentals

Terms & conditions
==================

**Effective Date: February 14, 2021**

This Privacy Policy (“**Policy**”) describes how GW50, LLC (“**GW50, LLC**”; “**Company**”, “**us**”, “**our**”, and “**we**”) collects, uses and shares information from and about users of its website https://gigworker.com/ (the “**Site**”).  This Policy also describes the measures that GW50 takes to protect the information, your options for choice and access, and how you can contact us about privacy practices.  This Policy is part of our Terms of Use (the “**Terms**”) for the Site.

GW50 respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy.

This policy applies to information we collect

* On this Site;
* In email, text, and other electronic messages between you and this Site;

It does not apply to information collected by:

* Us offline or through any other means, including on any other website operated by GW50 or any third party (including our affiliates and subsidiaries); or
* Any third party (including our affiliates and subsidiaries), including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from or on the Site.

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Site. By accessing or using this Site, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time (see Updates to Privacy Policy). Your continued use of this Site after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.

1. **What We Collect**

1.1. **“Personal Information”,** as used in this Policy, is information that identifies you as an individual or relates to an identifiable person.  We collect Personal Information from you in the following ways:

We collect Personal Information when you submit it to us, including when you ask to be added to our mailing list, contact us through the Site, participate in a community forum, create an account through our Site or otherwise directly give it to us, by email or otherwise.  The Personal Information you submit may include your name, email address, username, and affiliated website.

We may also, to the extent permitted by applicable law, receive Personal Information about you from third parties including social media services or other commercially available sources.  The Personal Information we receive from third parties may include your name, contact information, information about your transactions, relationships with product and service providers, and your use of certain applications.  For example, if you access our Site through a social media service or connect our Site to a social media service, we may collect your user ID and/or user name associated with that social media service and any information the social media service shares with us, such as your profile picture or email address.  The information we obtain depends on your privacy settings on the applicable social media service.  When you access the Site through social media services or when you connect our Site to social media services, you are authorizing us to collect, store, and use such information in compliance with this Policy.

1.2.  **“Other Information”,** as used in this Policy, is any information that is not intended to disclose your specific identity to us, such as usage data, browser information, information collected through cookies and other tracking technologies, demographic information, geolocation data obtained with your consent where required by applicable law, and aggregated data.  We collect Other Information from you in the following ways:

We collect Other Information when you submit it to us.  This may include your password or other information, such as your birthday or occupation, that you voluntarily provide to us through the Site.

We may receive Other Information about you from third parties, including, for example, demographic data, social media account number, information about your interests or information about your activities on other websites.

We and our service providers may automatically collect information through browser cookies and other tracking technologies (collectively “**Cookies**”) when you visit our Site to provide and improve the Site, and to display relevant content, products, services and advertising. Cookies are small files placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Site. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse Cookies, our system will issue Cookies when you direct your browser to our Site.  Through the use of Cookies, we may obtain information about your computer or device, including computer operating system type and device characteristics, Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, browser language, and the name of your Internet service provider, and your activities, including the website you visited before browsing our Site, pages you viewed, how long you spent on a page, the number and frequency of your visits, access times, and other information about your use of and actions on our Site.

1.3. Information We Collect Through Automatic Data Collection Technologies

As you navigate through and interact with our Site, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns, including:

* Details of your visits to our Site, including traffic data, location data, logs, and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Site;
* Information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system, and browser type.

The information we collect automatically helps us to improve our Site and to deliver a better and more personalized service, including by enabling us to:

* Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.
* Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Site according to your individual interests.
* Speed up your searches.
* Recognize you when you return to our Site.

2\. **How We Use Your Information**

We may use your Personal Information for the purposes set forth below.  We may use and disclose Other Information for any purpose; provided that if such Other Information is considered Personal Information under applicable law or if we combine Other Information with your Personal Information, we will treat such information as Personal Information.

We may use your Personal Information:

* To present our Site and its contents to you.
* To provide you with information, products, or services that you request from us.
* To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it.
* To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection.
* To notify you about changes to our Site or any products or services we offer or provide though it.
* To allow you to participate in interactive features on our Site.
* In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.
* For any other purpose with your consent.

2.1.  **Use of Cookies**

Third parties, such as analytics providers, ad networks, and advertisers, may use Cookies to track your online activities over time and across third party websites, apps and devices.  We may not have access to these Cookies, but we may use information obtained through the use of these Cookies to improve our products and services.  The information we obtain through these Cookies, along with Personal Information and Other Information we collect from your use of the Site (including through use of any Cookies that we employ to collect information from our Site), can be used to help improve our content, remember your preferences, personalize offerings, and show you advertisements that may be tailored to your interests.  These third party companies may also transfer this information to other parties where required to do so by law, or where such other parties process the information on their behalf.

Specifically, we and our service providers may use advertising Cookies to deliver ads that we think will be relevant to you and your interests.  We may use advertising Cookies to customize the advertising and content you receive on our Site, conduct interest-based advertising, limit the number of times you see the same ad on our Site, help measure the effectiveness of advertising campaigns, and conduct market research.  These Cookies remember what you have looked at or purchased on our Site and other sites, and may be combined with other information acquired from third parties such as demographics and other marketing information.  We may share this information with other organizations, such as advertisers, in accordance with applicable law.  Third party advertisers and other organizations may also use their own Cookies to collect information about your activities on our Site and/or the advertisements you have clicked on.  This information, which may be combined with other marketing information acquired from third parties, may be used to provide advertisements on our Site and third party sites that they think will be of interest to you based on content you have viewed.  Third party advertisers may also use this information to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to track aggregate usage statistics.

Some content or applications, including advertisements, on the Site are served by third parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers, and application providers. These third parties may use cookies to collect information about you when you use our Site. The information they collect may be associated with your personal information or they may collect information, including personal information, about your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioral) advertising or other targeted content.

We are not responsible for any third-party websites, apps, advertisements, content or special offers linked or referenced on our Site.  We do not control any Cookies or other similar devices placed on our Site by third parties, such as those that may be embedded in third-party advertising.  We are not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties.  Once you leave our Site or click an advertisement, or sign up for a special offer, the applicable third party privacy policy will apply.  If you have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, you should contact the responsible provider directly. For information about how you can opt out of receiving targeted advertising from many providers, see Your Rights and Choices.

2.2.  **To Provide Content and to Operate, Maintain and Improve Our Site**

We use Personal Information and Other Information we collect from and about you to operate, maintain, and improve our Site, including to (i) deliver the content, products and services offered through our Site or that users request, (ii) to create and manage your accounts, and (iii) allow you to engage with us (e.g., to comment on content or send us Feedback (as defined in the Terms).  We may also use the information we collect from you to analyze website use and improve and customize the content, layout, and services of our Site.

2.3.  **To Provide (and Allow Third Parties to Provide) Advertising and Interest-Based Advertising**

We and our service providers may use any of the information we collect from and about you to allow us to provide ads about products and services tailored to your individual interests when you use our Site.  We may work with third party advertising companies, advertisers and ad networks who help deliver these ads to you.  These third parties may collect and use information about your activities on our Site and on other websites to provide ads to you that are believed to be consistent with your interests.  Please see additional details in Section 2.1 above.

### Mediavine Programmatic Advertising (Ver 1.1)

The Website works with Mediavine to manage third-party interest-based advertising appearing on the Website. Mediavine serves content and advertisements when you visit the Website, which may use first and third-party cookies. A cookie is a small text file which is sent to your computer or mobile device (referred to in this policy as a “device”) by the web server so that a website can remember some information about your browsing activity on the Website.

First party cookies are created by the website that you are visiting. A third-party cookie is frequently used in behavioral advertising and analytics and is created by a domain other than the website you are visiting. Third-party cookies, tags, pixels, beacons and other similar technologies (collectively, “Tags”) may be placed on the Website to monitor interaction with advertising content and to target and optimize advertising. Each internet browser has functionality so that you can block both first and third-party cookies and clear your browser’s cache. The “help” feature of the menu bar on most browsers will tell you how to stop accepting new cookies, how to receive notification of new cookies, how to disable existing cookies and how to clear your browser’s cache. For more information about cookies and how to disable them, you can consult the information at [All About Cookies](https://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/).

Without cookies you may not be able to take full advantage of the Website content and features. Please note that rejecting cookies does not mean that you will no longer see ads when you visit our Site. In the event you opt-out, you will still see non-personalized advertisements on the Website.

The Website collects the following data using a cookie when serving personalized ads:

* IP Address
* Operating System type
* Operating System version
* Device Type
* Language of the website
* Web browser type
* Email (in hashed form)

Mediavine Partners (companies listed below with whom Mediavine shares data) may also use this data to link to other end user information the partner has independently collected to deliver targeted advertisements. Mediavine Partners may also separately collect data about end users from other sources, such as advertising IDs or pixels, and link that data to data collected from Mediavine publishers in order to provide interest-based advertising across your online experience, including devices, browsers and apps. This data includes usage data, cookie information, device information, information about interactions between users and advertisements and websites, geolocation data, traffic data, and information about a visitor’s referral source to a particular website. Mediavine Partners may also create unique IDs to create audience segments, which are used to provide targeted advertising.

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices to opt-in or opt-out of this data collection, please visit [National Advertising Initiative opt out page](https://thenai.org/opt-out/). You may also visit [Digital Advertising Alliance website](http://optout.aboutads.info/#/) and [Network Advertising Initiative website](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#) to learn more information about interest-based advertising. You may download the AppChoices app at [Digital Advertising Alliance’s AppChoices app](https://youradchoices.com/appchoices) to opt out in connection with mobile apps, or use the platform controls on your mobile device to opt out.

For specific information about Mediavine Partners, the data each collects and their data collection and privacy policies, please visit [Mediavine Partners](https://www.mediavine.com/ad-partners/).

2.4.  **To Allow Social Sharing Functionality**

If you log in with, or connect a social media service account to, our Site, we may use Personal Information and Other Information to facilitate your sharing of information between our Site and your social media service.

2.5.  **To Contact You**

We may send you materials about promotions, upcoming events, and other news related to the content offered on our Site and products and services from our selected partners.  We may use and combine any of the Personal Information and Other Information we collect to assist us in sending you these materials.  We may also contact you to respond to your comments, questions, requests or other Feedback and to provide customer service.

2.6.  **To Protect Our Rights and the Rights of Others**

We may use your Personal Information, as we find necessary or appropriate in our discretion, and as permitted by law to: resolve disputes or troubleshoot problems; comply with law and respond to lawful requests from public and government authorities and legal processes; protect, enforce, or defend the legal rights, privacy, safety, or property of GW50 or its employees, agents and contractors (including enforcement of our agreements, policies and Terms); protect the safety, privacy, and security of users of our Site or other third parties; enforce contractual and intellectual property rights; and protect against fraud and other unlawful activity or for risk management purposes.

 3. **How We Share Your Information**

3.1. **Our Disclosure of Personal Information and Other Information**

We may disclose Personal Information that we collect or you provide as described in this privacy policy:

* To our subsidiaries and affiliates.
* To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it.
* For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.
* With your consent.

We may also disclose your personal information:

3.1.1. **To Allow Third-Party Service Providers to Help Us Operate Our Site**

We may provide your Personal Information to contractors, service providers, and other third parties who help us operate our Site, by, for example: developing or supporting content, products and features; sending email messages on our behalf; processing data or statistics; and serving, customizing or delivering marketing.  These third party service providers are required to protect Personal Information entrusted to them and not use it for any other purpose than the specific service they are providing on our behalf.

3.1.2. **To Allow Social Sharing Functionality**

If you log in with, or connect a social media service account to, our Site, you are authorizing us to share information we collect from and about you with the social media service provider, and you acknowledge that the use of such information by the social media service will be governed by its privacy policy.  If you do not want your Personal Information shared in this way, please do not connect your social media service account with our Site, and do not participate in social sharing on the Site.

3.1.3. **To Protect Our Rights or the Rights of Others**

There may be instances when we may disclose your Personal Information, including situations where we have a good faith belief that such disclosure is necessary in order to: comply with law and respond to requests from public and government authorities and legal processes or court order; protect, enforce, or defend the legal rights, privacy, safety, or property of GW50 or its employees, agents and contractors (including enforcement of our agreements, policies and Terms), including for billing and collection purposes; protect the rights, safety, privacy, and security of users of GW50, our customers, our Site or other third parties; enforce contractual and intellectual property rights; and protect against fraud and other unlawful activity or for risk management purposes, to the extent permitted by applicable law.

3.1.4.  **In the Case of a Merger, Sale of Assets or Bankruptcy**

If we sell all or part of our business or assets, or are otherwise involved in a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, liquidation, or other sale or transfer of all or part of our business or assets, whether as a going concern or as part of a bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, we may transfer your Personal Information to the party or parties and their advisors involved in that transaction.

3.2. **Information You Make Public through Use of Our Site**

Certain features on our Site, including community forums or comment posting features, give you an opportunity to interact with us and others.  When you use these features, any information you choose to submit, including the information requested from you in order to participate in such feature and the information included in your post, may be publicly available to anyone, including other users, search engines, advertisers, and anyone else with access to the Site.  We are not responsible for any information you choose to submit and make public through these interactive features.

4\. **How We Protect Personal Information**

We have implemented reasonable measures to safeguard Personal Information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration, and disclosure. However, no one can guarantee the complete safety of your information.  The safety and security of your information also depends on you. You acknowledge and agree that the security, integrity and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through the Site cannot be guaranteed and that you use the Site and send us information at your own risk.  We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site. If you have reason to believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure, please contact us immediately at the address below.

5\. **Your Rights and Choices**

We strive to provide you with choices regarding the Personal Information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information:

5.1 **Opt Out of Direct Marketing**

You may opt out of receiving electronic communications from us (including our newsletter or promotions), by contacting us at the address provided below or following the unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.  Please note that there are certain service notifications that you may not opt out of, such as notifications of changes to your account.

5.2. **Opt Out of Interest-Based Advertising**

You may opt out of online interest-based advertising by taking the steps detailed below.

By using the Site with your browser setting adjusted to accept Cookies, you consent to the use of Cookies by us, our service providers and advertisers as set forth in this Policy.  Many browsers are set to accept Cookies until you change your settings.  You can remove and reject cookies from our Site through your browser settings.  Most browsers will tell you how to change your browser settings to notify you when a Cookie is being set or updated, or to restrict or block certain types or all Cookies.  Please consult the “Help” section of your browser for more information.  Your device settings may also allow you to prohibit mobile app platforms from sharing certain information obtained by automatic processes with us.

Advertising Cookies on our Site include Google Adsense.  For further information, including how to opt out, please see: [https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/partners/](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/partners/).

Analytics Cookies on our Site include Google Analytics.  For further information, including how to opt out, please see: [https://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/learn/privacy.html](https://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/learn/privacy.html).

Opting out of advertising Cookies does not remove advertising from our Site; instead it means the ads you will see may not be matched to your interests.

If you make updates to your browser or device settings, or use an online link to opt out of Cookies, those updates apply to the device where you made the changes.  Please note that disabling or blocking Cookies could affect how certain functions on our Site work for you. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this site may then be inaccessible or not function properly.

We do not control third parties’ collection or use of your information to serve interest-based advertising. However these third parties may provide you with ways to choose not to have your information collected or used in this way. You can opt out of receiving targeted ads from members of the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) on the NAI’s website.

5.3. **How to Access, Correct, Update or Delete Your Personal Information**

You can access, correct, update or delete your Personal Information by contacting us at the address below.  You can also object to or restrict the processing of your Personal Information.  You can also exercise any rights you are entitled to under law.

Where you have provided your consent to our use of your Personal Information, you can withdraw your consent and we will apply your preferences going forward.  We may need to retain certain information for recordkeeping purposes and/or to complete any transactions you began prior to requesting such change or deletion.

6\. **California Consumers**

We do not meet the conditions as outlined in Section 1798.140 of the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (the “CCPA”) and therefore are not subject to CCPA requirements. For specific information related to your ability to access and correct your personal information, _see_ How to Access, Correct, Update or Delete Your Personal Informationabove.

7\. **GDPR Notice**

In compliance with the European Union (“EU”) General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”), we may rely upon one or more legal bases defined in the GDPR to collect, use, share and otherwise process the personal information of individuals located in the EU, including where:

* Necessary to perform a contract we have with you, such as our terms of engagement, and to provide the services;
* You have consented to the processing (in which case you may revoke your consent at any time);
* Necessary for us to comply with a legal obligation, or to establish, exercise or defend legal claims;
* Necessary to protect your vital interests or those of others;
* Necessary in the public interest; and
* Necessary for the purposes of GW50 or a third party’s legitimate interests, provided that those interests are not overridden by your interests or fundamental rights and freedoms.

Where we collect, use, disclose and otherwise process your information based on legitimate interests, we may rely on the following interests:

* Marketing our products: We use your information as necessary to pursue our legitimate interests in marketing our products to you. For example, where permitted by digital marketing law, we may contact you by email to let you know of products you might be interested in.
* Providing, improving and developing our products: We use your information as necessary to pursue our legitimate interests in tailoring and improving our products. For example, we may send you a survey or questionnaire to understand your experience in purchasing from us.

If you are located in the EU, under certain circumstances, you may have certain legal rights under the GDPR, including:

* To access the personal data we maintain about you
* To receive information about how we process your personal data
* To correct your personal data
* To have your personal data erased
* To object to or restrict how we process your personal data
* To request your personal data be transferred to a third party
* To withdraw any consent you may have given us to process your personal data

If you are an EU resident, you have the right to object to our processing that is based on legitimate interests by contacting us at the address or number below. If you are located in the EU and you believe that we have infringed your rights under the GDPR, please contact us by sending an email to info \[at\] gigworker \[dot\] com.

 8. **Other Important Information**

8.1.  **Updates to Privacy Policy**

This Policy is effective as of the Effective Date set forth above.  We have the right to change or update this Policy at our discretion and without notice to you.  This Policy is subject to occasional revision and, if we make any material changes, we will notify you by posting a prominent notice on our Site indicating we have updated this Policy.  Continued use of our Site following these changes means you acknowledge you have read and accept the revised Policy.

8.2. **Do Not Track Disclosure**

Some browsers or other tools include “Do Not Track” (DNT) features which, when turned on, send a signal to websites you visit indicating you do not wish to be tracked across websites over time.  We do not currently respond to DNT signals.

8.3. **Children Under 13**

Our Site is not intended for children under 13 years of age.  No one under age 13 may provide any Personal Information to or on the Site.  We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under 13.  If you are under 13, do not use this Site or provide any information on this Site.  If we learn we have collected or received Personal Information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information.  If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at the address below.

9\. **Contact Us**

We welcome your comments or questions about this Policy.  You may contact us at our address:

GW50, LLC

Attn: Privacy Policy Department

12925 West Dodge Road, Suite 106A

Omaha, NE 68154

Email: info \[at\] gigworker \[dot\] com

Please do not disclose any sensitive Personal Information (e.g., information related to racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religion or other beliefs or health, social security numbers, or criminal background information) when contacting us.

Gigworker.com helps gig workers find work and companies scale by outsourcing.

Outsourcing & Work

[

Outsource

Freelancers & outsourcing companies](https://www.gigworker.com/#outsource-something)[

Work

Jobs, side hustles, and gig resources](https://www.gigworker.com/#find-a-gig)[

Platforms

Platform-specific guides & information](https://gigworker.com/gig-headquarters)

Company

Other Resources

Copyright © Gigworker 2024. All rights reserved.
